#Encodergasm Presents
～
Hello, gentlemen.
（東風(トンプウ)）ハロー ジェントルメン
はああ…
I have come to take your lives.
お前の命を もらいに来た
（スパイク）ふう
Hello, boy.
（東風）ハロー ボーイ
ニヘヘ
（スパイク）うっ
ぐっ はっ…
（東風）ひぃ
（パトカーのサイレン）
（ボブ）お前の相棒も
つくづく不運だな ジェット
Your partner sure is unlucky, Jet.
（ジェット）まあ もともと
あまりついてる男じゃないが…
Well, he wasn't all that lucky to begin with.
（ボブ）この一件は まずい
This case is especially bad.
こればっかりは
手を引いたほうがいいぜ
It would be better to not get yourselves involved in this one.
（ジェット）
いいから早く答えろよ
I don't care, just answer me.  Now.
I'm telling you this for your own sake, and...
お前のために言ってるんだぜ
それに あまり この件に関わると
こっちだってやばいんだ
...if you get too involved in this, I'm gonna get in trouble, too.
スゥー…
（ジェット）なあ ボブ
You know, Bob...
You're the only person I can rely on right now.
こんなことを頼めるのは
お前しかいねえ
お前に悪いようにはせんさ
だから…
I'll make sure it won't be bad for you.  So...
（ボブ）
毎回 同じこと言ってねえか？
Don't you say that every time?
Really... you always have been a guy that likes to get into trouble.
全く 昔から
厄介ごとの好きな男だぜ
All right, this is only a rumor, but...
いいか？
これは あくまでうわさだが…
マッドピエロって名前を
聞いたことがあるか？
...have you heard of the name "Mad Pierrot"?
（エド）ん ん んん ふふん
（フェイ）いたいた
うわさのミイラ男
There he is, the rumored mummy.
So, I heard you got beaten up by some weird guy?
何でも へんてこな おっさんに
やられたんだって？
I recall you were sleeping like this once before.
前にも そんなかっこで
寝てたわよねえ
全く 進歩のない男ね
You really haven't shown any improvement.
ま 私には関係ないけど
Oh well, it doesn't have anything to do with me.
Don't you end up in situations like that because you never behave?
大体 日ごろの行いが悪いから
そういう目に遭うんじゃないの？
ま 私には関係ないけど
Well, I have nothing to do with it.
So, since I have nothing to do with it, if you'll excuse me...
（フェイ）ま そんなわけで
関係ない 私は失礼しまーす
お大事に
Take care.
（ボブ）殺されたのは
ＩＳＳＰの偉いさん
The victim was a high-ranking guy from the ISSP.
He was the seventh victim.
これで７人目だ
（ジェット）何だって？
What did you say?
Can't blame you.  This is top-secret.
（ボブ）知らねえのも無理はねえ
こいつは極秘扱いだ
どうやらお偉いさん方 この件は
世間に知られたくないらしい
Apparently those higher-ups don't want the world to find out about this.
Why?
（ジェット）なんでだ？
その相棒 やばいぜ
Your partner is in deep trouble.
やつは完璧な殺人マシンだ
The guy is a perfect killing machine.
今までに やつの姿を見て
生き延びた人間はいないって話だ
They say that nobody who has seen his face has made it out alive.
たまたま現場を逃れた者も―
Even those lucky enough to escape'll be tracked down to the ends of the world...
どこまでも追いかけて
必ず息の根を止めるんだ
...and they always wind up dead.
やつは ほほ笑みと共に現れ
ほほ笑みと共に去っていくらしい
They say he appears with a smile, and he leaves with a smile.
（ボブ）そう やつこそ
マッドピエロと呼ばれる
Yeah, he is the mysterious assassin known as Mad Pierrot...
幻の殺し屋 “東風”だ
...Tongpu.
（東風）ハハハハハハハ…
（エド）んにゃあ…
（フェイ）ちっ ああ
（エド）フェイフェイ
すぱすぱフェイフェイー
Faye-Faye!
Puff, puff!  Faye-Faye!
すぱすぱフェイフェイー
Puff, puff!  Faye-Faye...
（フェイ）ちょっと あんた―
Hey you, can you stop saying my name twice like that?
その“フェイフェイ”って
２回言うの やめてくんない？
フェイフェイ
変なメールが来た来たよー
Faye-Faye, a weird mail came, came.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
ねえねえねえねえ
…ったく もう少しで私も
来るところだったのに
...and I woulda been done if I had a little more time...
（フェイ）読めないでしょ
（エド）にゃあ
I can't read it!
（フェイ）ん？“ハロー ボーイ”
"Hello, boy.  I'll invite you to a wonderful party..."
“すてきなパーティーに
ご招待しよう”
Wait, this is...
ちょっと これって…
いい？
このメールが来たことは―
Listen, keep the fact that this mail came a secret from Spike.
スパイクには
内緒にすんのよ
内緒？
Secret?
Why?
なんで？ 内緒 なんで？
Why secret?
そうしないと あのばかは…
If we don't, that idiot...
（スパイク）
飛び出していっちまうってか？
...will run out to meet him?
It's a secret, secret mail!
内緒内緒のメールだよー
ふうん
“スペースランド”か
Space Land?
Pretty considerate of him to hold the party there.
気の利いたパーティー会場だな
その格好で行く気？
You're gonna go like that?
まあ 仮装パーティーなら
ぴったりね
Well, it would be perfect if it was a masquerade.
今度ばっかりは
俺も年貢の納め時かもな
Maybe this one really will be the end of me...
Just kidding!
なーんて言ったら
助けに来てくれるのかな？
Would you come rescue me if I said that?
ばか
Idiot.
Idiot, idiot, idiot!
（エド）ばーかばーかばーか
アハハハハハハ
（ジェット）んん？ おい
Hey...
（エド）んん？
Oh, it's you, Ed.  Where's Spike?
エドか　スパイクは？
He went somewhere.
（エド）どっか行ったよ
What?
なにい？
Not that this is anything new.  That idiot...
今に始まったこっちゃねえが
あのばか…
Idiot, idiot?
ばかばか？
（ジェット）エド 頼みがある
Ed, I have a favor to ask.
What, what?
なになに？
いって　あっあ…
Hello!
（東風）ハロー ウエルカム
Welcome!
Yo...
よう
ハーハハハハハハハハ
Let's party!
レッツパーティー
（パレードの音楽）
You can't enter here!
（天使）
ここは入っちゃいけないよ
ここは危ないよ　外で遊ぼうよ
It's dangerous in here!  Let's play outside!
Shut up!
（スパイク）やかましい
（天使）ここは危ないよ
It's dangerous in here!  Let's play outside!
外で遊ぼうよ  ここは危ないよ
It's dangerous in here!
（スパイク）くっ ぐ…
It's dangerous in here!  Let's play outside!
（天使）
ここは危ないよ  外で遊ぼうよ
Hi!
ハーイ
（スパイク）ぐっ くっ
くふぅ
（スパイク）ぐわあ
All right, Ed...
（ジェット）いいか？ エド
まずは
First, enter the ISSP's main computer, and look for section 13.
ＩＳＳＰのメインコンピューターに
入り込んで―
“セクション13”を
捜し出してくれ
Aye, aye!
あいあーい
That's the section that doesn't exist to the general public.
そいつは公には 存在しないことに
なっているセクションだ
It's a pretty tall order.  Can you do it?
かなりの難物だが できるか？
Yup!
あいー
（東風）ハハハハハハハハ
アハハハハハハハ…
アーハハハハハハ
ハハハハハハハハ
アハハハハハハ
アハハハハハハハ…
アハハハハハハハ
Hello!
（マスコット）あっ あっ あう
あ お は は お お…
はお はお はお…
わし わし わお…
Found it!
見つけたー
After you open it, find the file with the code name "Tongpu."
（ジェット）そいつを開いたら
コードネーム“東風”の
ファイルを探してくれ
Yup!
（エド）あーい
（スパイク）うあっ ええ
うっ ん う…
（東風）ハハハハハハ…
う！ くっ くわっ
（エド）ぬあー
ハーハハハハハハハ…
アーハハハハハハハ
（スパイク）ぬあー
Peek-a...
いなーいなーい ばー
...BOO!
（幹部）
ＩＳＳＰ 暗殺能力向上実験
ISSP Assassination Ability lmprovement Experiment.
被検体 カルテナンバー46
Experiment sample chart number 46.
Code name: Tongpu.
コードネーム“東風”
Confirmed a strong regression of the mind during...
実験中に
精神の著しい退行現象を確認
...the experiment.  Experiment was canceled.
以後 実験は中止
Sample to be permanently kept in a quarantine facility.
隔離施設にて永久収容とする
（ジェット）初めは復讐のために
収容所を脱走したんだろうが
In the beginning, he escaped from the facilities to seek revenge...
...but now he seems to be enjoying the actual act of killing.
今じゃ 殺し自体を
楽しんでるのかもしれん
His mind must be continuing to regress.
やつの精神は
今も退行を続けているはずだ
So, he's like a child with superhuman fighting abilities.
やつは超人的な戦闘能力を持った
子供ってわけか
Really...
全く　ガキほど純粋で
残酷なもんはねえ
There is nothing as pure and cruel as children.
（スパイク）うう あ あ
It's show time!
（東風）イッツ ショーターイム
ハハ アハ アハハハ…
That was unnecessary!
（スパイク）余計なまねを
フーハハハハハハ…
フーハハハハハハハハー
（スパイク）ああっ だっ
Hello, hello...
（ピエロ）ハロー ハロー
Hello!  Hello!
ハロー ハロー
Hello...
ハロー
（パレードの音楽）
（東風）ハハハーハハハ…
（スパイク）んん はっ
くっ…
（東風）アハハハハハ
はあ あ あああ…
（遠くに聞こえるパレードの音楽）
うっ ひい！
うう…
T-That hurts!
痛いよ　う ううあ あうー
It hurts!
痛いよ アハハ ああ
It hurts!!
痛いよー アハハハ…
ああ ああ 痛いよー
It HURTS!!
Hurts...
いい… ママー アハハハ
Mommy, it hurts!
痛いよー オホホ オオ　オホホ
MOMMY!!
ママー アハハー ああ
えー えー エへー
It hurts...  Mommy!
痛いよー ホホーホ
Spike!  All right, we figured out what he is!  He's...
（ジェット）スパイク いいか
やつの正体が分かった
（ジェット）やつは…
（スパイク）いや…
No.  I don't need it anymore.
ああ もういいんだ
It all ended just now.
もう終わったとこだ
Too much time has passed by...
Aishiteta to nageku niwa
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
Amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
Mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
lyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
Kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
The real folk blues.
The real folk blues
I only want to know what true sadness is.
Honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
Sitting in muddy water...
Doro no kawa ni tsukatta
...isn't such a bad life...
Jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...if it ends after the first time...
Ichido kiri de owaru nara
～
（スパイク）最近なんか
おかしいと思ったんだよな
I knew there was something fishy going on lately.
So, that's what it was!
（フェイ）
そういうことだったんだー
（ジェット）
んん？ 何の話 してんだ？
What are you guys talking about?
You really can't judge people by their looks.
（スパイク）
人は見かけによらないっつーか
Honestly disgusting.
（フェイ）不潔だわ  本当
Hey, hey, what are you guys talking about?
（ジェット）
おいおい 何の話だよ
I never thought it would be a teenage girl...
（スパイク）まさか10代の娘にな
（フェイ）軽蔑しちゃうわね
It makes me despise him.
Who are you talking about?
（ジェット）誰の話なんだよ
Next episode: Boogie Woogie Feng Shui.
（スパイク）
次回「ブギ･ウギ･フンシェイ」
I didn't do anything!
（ジェット）俺は何もしてねえぞ